We building an empire so when we expand.
I'll put y'all in charge.
You really stealing and selling my shit
- without telling me?
- I don't want her
- anywhere near the business.
- It's 1.5. niña.
to buy your life. You
got that lying around?
What if I can offer you the recipe?
It is the DEA. They got an undercover
inside the Villanueva operation.
Arrest the Villanuevas.
whoever we get after that...
The real prize here is the
pilot and his partner.
Keep your eyes straight ahead.
Somebody's watching the office.
You think this is a game?
No. I don't think it's a fucking game.
- This shit ends tonight.
- No more barrio manhunts.
- It's done.
- Wanna know who killed your friends?
- Why would you do that?
- 'Cause you're gonna tell us
how to cook up that rock.
I'm funny now. bitch?
[BOTH GRUNTING. YELLING]
I need you to come to the
club right the fuck now.
- About fucking time.
- We got some heat.
Once you are ready to
resume our pick-ups.
- Matt goes free.
- Do not fucking hurt him.
Betraying your best friend
ain't exactly a quick decision.
Franklin asked us to
find out before we met.
I knew. I just wouldn't give him up.
It's three hours supervised visitation.
Well. all right. Let's
go cook some rock.
I did everything for you.
- I let you back in!
- You're diseased. Lucia.
And every day you'll hear my voice.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[COINS CLINKING]
[QUIET. DARK MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
I'm sorry. chula.
I haven't called Gabriella yet.
I need your help showing
her how to cook it.
_
Where are you?
She's here waiting.
I'm gonna tell her the pilot
will come in the morning.
Oso...
♪ ♪
_
You did what you had to. chula.
[DOOR CRASHES]
DEA. hands up!
Don't move!
_
- Wait. what?
- [SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Run. Oso. run!
- Get out of it!
- Stop right there!
- Put it down!
- Hands up. hands up!
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
♪ ♪
Fuck! Fucking bitch!
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
[HORNS HONK. SIRENS WAIL]
Look. I don't understand.
What do you mean. James
is no longer here?
You must have been gone
a while. Mr. McDonald.
Was he transferred?
If you'll wait a moment.
[CHATTER. PHONES RINGING]
[SIGHS]
I'm so sorry.
but Mr. Grace is unavailable to see you.
This is ridiculous. William knows me.
I'm sure he won't mind if
I just have a quick word.
Mr. Grace can't see you right now.
You perhaps should make an appointment?
I just need to know
what happened to James.
I already told you. Mr. Ballard
is no longer in his position.
No... and I understand.
but what I'm asking
is why he's no longer in his position.
Well. I'm afraid I don't know that.
Okay. do you know if maybe
he left behind any files
pertaining to his work
with the Los Angeles field station?
Right.
'Cause you know nothing.
And your boss won't see me.
I strongly advise you to make...
Yeah. make an appointment.
Yeah. no. I got that.
You already said that.
and I already told you
that I don't have time to wait for that.
- Okay.
- Actually. you know what?
- What?
- I understand.
- Okay.
- Very clearly.
- Thank you so much.
- Good.
Have a nice day.
[FUNKY MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[MEN CHATTERING]
Remember when we were kids.
Pops would come outside.
whistle real loud.
meaning it's time for dinner.
I used to hate that. Y'all live so far.
Yeah. me and Kev had to walk
all the way back to the projects.
Yeah. that was a long time ago.
What we doin' here now. Saint?
Getting more interested in real estate.
Guess my moms taught me a thing or two
without even realizing it.
but it's time to buy.
You moving out of Jerome's?
This gonna be your new spot?
Nah. not mine. Yours.
- Other one's yours.
- No.
[CHUCKLES] Now. your shit
got the big back yard
for all them damn kids.
and your shit got the
master for the ladies. huh?
You bought us a fucking house?
- Yeah.
- [LAUGHING] Oh. shit.
Check your shit out.
[LAUGHING] This is dope.
♪ Never get another chance ♪
- What's wrong?
- [DOOR OPENS]
Nothing. man.
I was just thinking about
your pop's whistle. too.
[DOOR CLOSES]
- I used to hate that shit.
- [CHUCKLES]
Always meant the end of us hanging out.
Trying to get that one.
The owner ain't trying to sell.
Yet.
Oh. yeah?
All three of us on the same block.
That's the shit we always dreamed about.
Yeah.
Hey. Saint. I don't know if
I ever told you. but. uh...
Thanks.
For everything.
Silence isn't gonna help. Gustavo.
I'll ask you again:
Where's Lucia?
Do you understand what
you're looking at?
Multiple homicides.
Conspiracy.
Trafficking and distribution.
I get it.
You think you can handle prison.
But we have ways of making that
a very difficult life for you.
For instance...
putting word out on the street
that you're a snitch
who ratted on La Fuerza.
Hmm?
Every Mexican prison gang in the U.S.
will know your name.
You'll be beaten and stabbed
until you're barely alive.
Now...
we can help you avoid that.
- I want a lawyer.
- [PAGER BEEPING]
- Yeah.
- [PHONE DIAL TONE]
[PHONE RINGING]
- Oso.
- Gustavo's going to jail
for a very long time unless
you turn yourself in.
- You fucking little bitch.
- Where's Pedro?
I don't know and I don't care.
You can't run from the U.S.
government. Lucia.
We'll find you anywhere in the world.
Turn yourself in.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[PHONE CLANKS]
[DIAL TONE]
♪ ♪
[UPBEAT LATIN MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You okay. chica?
You're not looking so good.
Just to be clear:
when I finish.
Gustavo and I are free.
Long as this works.
[KIDS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[DOG BARKING DISTANTLY]
Hey. Momma.
Take it you got my gift?
Wasn't sure it was you at first.
"Jason Peters."
[LAUGHING]
It's just my corporation.
It makes things easier.
- Your father and I...
- [SCOFFS]
Have discussed it.
I can't accept it.
What you mean... what you
mean you can't accept it?
You was gonna lose the house.
Then I'll lose it.
Your father and I will start
looking for a new place.
Jesus Christ. why is it so hard
to do a good fucking thing for you?
- Watch your language with me.
- No.
You played by the rules
and you got screwed.
I'm making up my own rules.
And I bought you a house. Momma.
- In cash.
- Illegal cash.
Using a fake name.
- Don't you see what's wrong with that?
- Wrong?
Kissing Tulfowitz's ass for ten years
and getting fired for
no reason is wrong.
Bank taking your house
for being a grand behind
on a fucking mortgage is wrong.
People getting killed in the street?
That's wrong.
Our people been getting
fucked over for centuries.
and you don't want a free
roof over your head?
Fine.
So don't take it.
See if I give a fuck.
Franklin...
[DOOR SLAMS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[INDISTINCT]
Your assistant said you
were in a meeting. so...
What are you doing here?
Just looking for James.
Getting the run-around.
What happened?
One day he was here. the next he wasn't.
- Why didn't you call me?
- [SCOFFS]
Why would I call you?
I'm sorry.
This isn't about us.
[SCOFFS]
And. um. I'm...
[SIGHS] I'm really...
I'm really sorry about.
uh. the way that...
I'm really sorry about
the way that we ended.
Julia...
This is really important.
It's always really important.
Please.
Not here. not now.
Meet me at Winston's.
Okay?
[DOOR CLOSES]
I always hated cooking.
I can see that.
You just let it harden.
Break it down and you're set.
So. we good?
You just bought your life.
Try smiling a little.
This doesn't even begin
to solve my problems.
_
- This is about being free.
- Free?
Oh. fuck... fucking kids.
Let me tell you something. chica:
In this life.
people die every day like that.
Unless you're not dead
or in jail. you're free.
Now get the fuck out of here.
Go handle your shit.
This bullshit's bringing me down.
_
- Toxic.
It's toxic.
Yeah. Sissy a proud woman.
- You know that.
- [GRUNTS]
Pride gonna fucking ruin that woman.
and I'm getting tired
of fighting for her.
Hey.
What's this?
Thank you for helping me out.
For everything.
Where you gonna go?
To LeRon's for a few days. and then...
I don't know.
Nephew.
Give us a minute.
I don't want you to go.
How I'm gonna stay here?
I don't exactly know.
but I know I don't want you
to leave. not like this.
You're all fucked up.
[PHONE RINGING]
You know. we ain't exactly
get to talk yet. right?
Right?
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- [PHONE RINGING]
Hey.
We got a problem.
Nah. I ain't got no time for that.
- Y'all handle it.
- It's Leon's girl.
She jacked the cookhouse.
What?
How the fuck that happen. man?
She showed up looking to cook.
but knocked Renny ass
out with a frying pan.
How much Wanda take?
- As much as she can carry.
- God damn. man.
Nigga. where the fuck was you at?
It wasn't my shift. Where was you at?
- Don't be putting this on me.
- All right. y'all hold tight.
All right? And we gonna grab Leon
and come pick you up.
God damn. man.
Hey.
What? You gotta do what you gotta do.
- I...
- Hey. come on. now.
Just chill.
Just chill for me.
- Okay? Come on.
- Okay.
All right. I'm gonna be back.
- All right.
[SIGHS]
LAPD has APBs out
on both Lucia and Pedro.
Pedro's in a fucking dumpster.
and Lucia's 50 miles away.
[SIGHS]
I got greedy.
You got fucking played is what happened.
[PAGER BEEPING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DIAL TONE]
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
[LINE CLICKS]
You're running out of options. Lucia.
Tell me your real name. and
I'll tell you what I want.
♪ ♪
My real name is Lorena.
[APPROACHING SIREN]
♪ ♪
Hands up! You're under arrest.
I wanna see Gustavo first.
Tony!
♪ ♪
Fine. Lorena.
You've got your deal.
Turn around. Turn the fuck around.
Does that make you feel tough?
[HISSES] Fuck!
- Let's go.
- They're tight.
♪ ♪
- [POUNDING ON DOOR]
- Yeah. I'm okay.
It's Marilyn I'm worried about.
Hey.
Where's she at?
Who's what?
- We said. where's the bitch at?
- Hey. hold up.
- We'll find her. all right? We'll find her.
- Search the crib.
[TV CHATTERING]
- Where's Wanda?
- Where you think. boy?
- Hold up.
- The fuck you going?
- Hell no. come here.
- [YELPS]
Uh-huh. mm-hmm.
- I ain't no Renny.
- What's the deal?
- What do you need?
- Yeah. caught her trying
- to sneak out the back.
- Why the fuck...
What the fuck did I say to you. huh?
Hey. baby. Um. I was just holding
- all of it. you know?
- All y'all shut up.
- I can't hear the TV.
- Because I cooked
- most of the shit.
- Need to teach her a lesson.
No. I wanna handle this shit. all right?
Thought you already did. Leon.
- What you doing with my rock?
- Your rock?
You out your goddamn mind?
Why are you so mad. baby?
- It's... we should do it together.
- How long have you been
- smoking this shit?
- Um...
Um. I don't know. It's all
just running together.
But. I don't think I
ever really stopped.
- Gotta get her off this shit.
- Wait a minute.
- Ow. that hurts! Where we going?
- No. no. no.
What you doing with my rock? Gimme that!
- Give me my rock! Give me my rock!
- Open the door.
- Gimme my fucking rock!
- Look at this shit.
Let me go! I don't wanna go!
Ow. that hurts!
[SCREAMING INDISTINCTLY]
Hey. young'un.
Hand... hand Auntie that pipe. please?
The Soviet Union's decision
not to take part in the
Los Angeles Olympics
threatens to snowball this
morning into a boycott
by other members of the Communist Bloc.
An influential Soviet journalist
reported this morning that the Kremlin
has already drawn up plans
for a Communist Bloc athletic meet
to be held in Bulgaria.
[TV CHATTER CONTINUES]
[SOFT MUZAK PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
♪ ♪
So what happened to James?
Rumors of a failed polygraph
then losing his security clearance.
but no one really knows.
He had a file.
and it was supposed to absolve me
if anything went wrong.
If you're expecting me to be surprised.
that James might have screwed you over.
I'm not.
Well. they're stonewalling me.
but I have to talk to whoever
took over for James.
Look...
we don't work together anymore.
We're certainly not
married anymore.
[TENSE MUSIC]
I can't help you.
♪ ♪
Fuck. Teddy.
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry about this.
You should know that. uh...
this thing blows up.
you won't be touched.
I'll make sure of that.
I'll take complete responsibility.
I'll shield everyone
except for James and the company.
That sounds like a threat.
You and Paul will both be protected.
I promise you that. but
you let it be known
to whoever is behind this
that I am not afraid to
make noise if I have to.
Do you have any idea what you're saying?
Yep. I know exactly what I'm saying.
You let them know.
I'll be here a few more hours.
♪ ♪
[SCOFFS]
I'll help you get the suppliers.
Two clean-cut American boys
running a hundred keys
a month from Colombia.
That's a lot of coke.
You don't get to dictate
the terms of your deal.
Then we don't have a deal.
[LAUGHS]
Come talk to me a minute.
Lucia. I'd be very fucking
careful if I were you.
She ain't gonna go for it.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
- I know they will.
- Okay. Don't you understand?
[CONVERSATION CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY]
What?
This makes us snitches.
Like Pedro.
_
Y qué?
[SIGHS]
Pedro betrayed his family.
We're handing over two white boys
who would do the same thing
to us given the chance.
I thought about running.
but not without you.
_
I'll tell them no deal.
[HISSES. GRUNTS]
I'm telling you. baby.
I feel like shit.
- I need to go back to Grandma's.
- I fucking told you
you ain't going nowhere. all right?
- [WHIMPERING]
- Sit the fuck down.
- Sit.
- [GRUNTS]
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WHIMPERS]
No more rock.
Ain't no more nothing.
Fuck you. [LAUGHS]
You'll never be more
than Franklin's lap dog.
[LAUGHING]
[GRUNTING. WHINING]
Where you going?
How... how long I gotta stay here?
Till you stop being fucking crazy.
- What if I gotta pee?
- Then pee on the carpet!
Getting rid of this
nasty-ass shag anyway.
[DISTANT SHOUTING]
[DOGS BARKING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hey. what the fuck?
I been paging you.
Needed your help with Wanda.
Been paging you all day.
Why you ain't answering me. huh?
- Fucking talk to me.
- It's all just bullshit. cuz.
Bullshit. you just got a fucking house.
Houses ain't even in our names. Lee.
Neither of them. I called the number?
I talked to the old owner.
Franklin's company owns this.
They ain't even our house. man.
Well. Franklin just keeping
our names out of it.
- Protecting us and shit.
- Protecting us from what?
Nigga. he just wants his workers happy.
He ain't give us this shit
- because he love us. Lee.
- Ungrateful motherfucker.
We ain't have shit a couple months ago.
You can't trust shit he say or do.
- You gotta trust me. Lee.
- You're trippin'. man.
You gotta do me a favor.
You my best friend. right?
Take care of my family if
something happens to me.
I will. Kev. but what
the fuck is going on?
He knew.
All along. that motherfucker knew
who killed Delroy and Victor.
and he ain't say shit.
How the fuck do you know that?
- 'Cause she told me.
- Who?
Don't matter who.
All that fucking matters is that...
Franklin is a fucking liar.
Don't trust Franklin.
You hear me?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Bye. Lee.
♪ ♪
[JEROME SHOUTING]
[SCRAPING]
God damn it...
[SCRAPING. BANGING]
- [GROANS]
- Shit.
You don't even want to know about it.
It's taken care of. though. I think.
Well. LeRon is waiting on me.
so why I gotta be here?
Let me show you something.
Come here.
- [SIGHS]
- Show you something.
- [GROANS]
- [LAUGHS]
Come here.
Hey.
[LAUGHS]
The fuck is that?
- You don't recognize it?
- No.
That's the bench where
we had our first date.
[LAUGHS] What?
Redondo Beach pier.
We was sitting right there.
Remember you was making fun of me?
Talking about. this some cheesy ass shit
- taking you down to Redondo Pier.
- [LAUGHS] Oh...
That's when I knew. right then.
- we was gonna be together.
- [LAUGHS]
Well. all I remember is
you left your wallet
at home. and I had to pay for dinner.
or so you said.
- I did leave my wallet.
- Mm. [LAUGHS]
Hey. was this bolted down?
Yeah. it took a while for
me to get this shit up.
- [LAUGHS]
- I looked kinda funny
trying to run with this damn thing.
[LAUGHS] And what if you had got caught?
Shit. come on.
I was all-city in the
backfield. you know?
Motherfuckers ain't gonna catch me.
I'm running. Touchdown. Yeah.
[LAUGHS]
Got something else to show you.
- All right?
- Okay.
- Stay right here. don't move.
- Mm-hmm.
You know. if I remember right
we was watching some men fish.
- You bring them back. too?
- [LAUGHING]
As of last week.
I done made $220.000.
That's 110.
That's yours.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
You know this ain't just
about the money. right?
♪ ♪
I... I know.
It's about respect.
♪ ♪
It's about being partners.
Us both making the decision
in everything that we do.
♪ ♪
I know when I'm messing up.
I'm gonna fix it.
♪ ♪
I love you. baby.
I love you. too. baby.
♪ ♪
[SOFT MUZAK PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[SIGHS]
You wanted to talk?
Talk.
You know what happened to James?
Yes.
- He tell you about me?
- Yes.
And may I ask who you are?
I work on compartmented
issues for the Director.
And it's my understanding
that you're not supposed
to contact us ever. especially the DDO.
And you're definitely not
supposed to be here.
much less threatening to make noise.
Mm-hmm. Well. I had to get
your attention somehow.
[SIGHS]
Now you have it.
So what is this about?
I am making huge strides in the effort.
Just tripled the allocation
completely on my own.
Pretty soon I won't
need Congress at all.
But. at the moment.
I got a little static I need relieved.
It's an investigation
that I need dropped.
Problem easily solved with
one interagency phone call.
- Which agency?
- DEA.
- [SCOFFS. SIGHS]
- You can say no if you want.
But understand that that means shutting
the entire operation down.
It means no more money.
it means no more guns.
To be safe. we'll have to destroy
Mr. Ballard's file on you.
Whatever you need to maintain
plausible deniability.
Might have to downgrade
your security clearance as well.
I can live with it.
[SIGHS]
You'll also need something to trade.
You tell him I can offer him
two Cali Cartel captains
who are in Los Angeles
right now.
[LIVELY LATIN MUSIC]
[CHICKEN CLUCKING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
♪ ♪
- [SNIFFING]
- Look at me.
You ready. marica? You
ready for some more?
Vamo. vamo. vamo. Oye. oye. oye.
[COUGHING]
I don't think fly boy likes it.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Too fucking bad for fly boy.
Oye. come on. you said you wanted to be
in the cocaine business.
- [GROANING. PANTING]
- You ready now. hijo de puta?
- [MOANING]
- Hello?
Hey. who is this?
Who is this?
I mean is it D... Danilo or... or Diego?
Ah. Reed.
Tell me we're ready to go.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
We are back on.
Is. uh. is Matt there?
Let me talk to Matt.
We are drowning your friend in coke.
and about to put razors
on the roosters so they can
slice each other to bits.
But the more important question is:
- Are we ready to go?
- Yeah.
We're back on. It's fixed.
- Just let me talk to Matt.
- [GROANING]
- Okay.
- [GASPS]
- Okay. breathe.
- Come... home... soon.
I'm seeing things. I'm seeing chickens.
[CHICKENS CLUCKING]
- I'm seeing chickens.
- Matt?
- Stop doing cocaine.
- He won't let me.
- [CLUCKING]
- So much.
My heart is starting to beat weird.
It's starting to beat
like it's to a song.
Like a Colombian lullaby.
Starting to beat to a Colombian lullaby.
Let's give him more coke.
- Huh?
- More coke. More coke.
No. no. no. stop.
Don't give him any more cocaine.
This is Diego.
Get this business back
up. or your friend
will find himself fighting
the razor-blade roosters.
- [PANTING]
- And he would lose.
That's what I'm saying. man. it's fixed.
I fixed it. it's good. I'm
gonna be home in a...
a few hours with. uh...
with the cash. okay?
- No more cocaine.
- We are just beginning.
Wait.
- [DIAL TONE]
- [SIGHS]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Hold his mouth. [SPEAKING SPANISH]
[MEN CHATTERING]
No. no...
[GASPS]
- [LAUGHING]
- Oh!
[PANTING. GROANING]
Hey!
Please. baby.
I just want a shower.
Please let me go. I'm getting all itchy.
- Soon.
- [WHIMPERS] Please!
Why are you doing this to me?
- 'Cause I love you.
- I love you too. baby.
so if you let me out of here. I'll stop.
I promise.
We can go World on Wheels.
Just us.
Like... like before all of this.
Please. Lee.
I love you so much.
Please help me.
I don't think you're ready yet.
Of course I'm ready!
Baby... [WHIMPERING] For you...
Come on. it'll be just like we said.
We could be...
we could be a happy family.
But you... but you gotta let me out.
Okay? 'Cause my arms is hurting.
Just for a little while. baby. please.
You gotta stay to sober up.
Fuck you. then!
Buster.
Stupid ass bitch nigga.
You ain't never gonna get
none of this ever again.
I'm gonna find me a real man
who don't have a problem
with his woman having
a little fucking fun!
[MUTTERING]
You the reason I'm stuck
like a fucking animal!
Wait. wait. wait. Where y'all going?
Y'all just gonna leave me here?
Fine. go be Franklin's bitch!
- Leon!
- Sorry. man.
You ain't nothing but a bitch!
She got it bad. huh?
Yeah. don't worry about her.
This is about Kev.
Yeah. I checked his new spot.
- Can't find him.
- He gone.
He all messed up. going
on about you lying
- and paying us off.
- Lying?
[CHUCKLES] Lying about what?
Delroy and Victor.
Exactly what did he say?
He said you knew all
along who killed them.
Didn't care. lied to us.
It was all about you
protecting your business.
God. that motherfucker.
He said he knew all this
'cause she told him.
She? She. who?
- I don't know.
- Lucia?
The... the Mexican?
Oh. my God.
- What?
- Leon...
Lucia wanted the recipe and I said no.
so she must have got it from Kev.
- But Kev wouldn't do that.
- For Delroy's killer?
- But you said she ain't know.
- Come on. we gotta find him.
I just talked to the LAPD.
They found a body.
Believed to be Pedro.
Got two bullets.
He was left in some shitty alley.
That's the best you could do?
You didn't have to kill him.
Especially if you were
thinking of cooperating.
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
- You don't?
- [GASPS]
You think you're so fucking ice cold?
- [GROWLS]
- Wait until I bring you
to the morgue to ID him.
They think feral cats got to him.
Fuck. [GASPING]
Pedro was having nightmares
about you two finding out
and killing him.
I'd hear him
yelling in the night.
Crying about what you did to his father.
Your uncle.
You're a fucking piece of shit.
You're a fucking sociopath.
[PAGER BEEPING]
Who is this?
What's this code? "8-12-4?"
8-12-4 is the pager code for a black kid
who sells rock all over South Central.
Sells for you?
I used to buy from him.
He supplies South Central?
- Where's he get his coke?
- I don't fucking know.
[HISSES]
Call him.
- Find out what he wants.
- [GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DIAL TONE]
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Tell me you didn't go behind my back
and get the process from Kevin.
I'm sorry. Franklin.
I told you I needed that recipe.
Jesus Christ.
Would have gotten out eventually.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What'd you give him in return?
Hmm? You tell him where to find
Delroy's killer?
You really gonna let Kev kill him
and start a fucking war.
♪ ♪
- Where's Kevin now?
- It doesn't matter.
- It'll be over soon.
- The fuck it don't.
Tell me where he is!
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Hello?
Is that true?
A war?
Tell him.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
♪ ♪
Your boy's going to Acuña Park.
You'd better hurry.
♪ ♪
Come on.
You're gonna ID this kid for me.
Get the fuck up when I'm talking to you.
Huh?
Let's go.
♪ ♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CHEERFUL CALLIOPE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
_
[BRAKES SQUEAKING]
Well?
Conejo's supposed to show up there soon.
- Get out of the car.
- No.
You wanted to know where it's happening.
Here we are.
You're gonna point out this
kid and his friend to me.
- Do you understand that?
- If there's gonna be
a shooting. I'm staying right here.
Go find them yourself. They're probably
the only black boys at the fucking park.
- You really think I'm gonna run now?
- You know what. Lucia?
I think you're capable of anything.
[CAR DOOR SLAMS]
♪ ♪
[KIDS CHATTERING]
Hi. Mommy!
♪ ♪
They'll know it was you. Kev.
They'll come after all of us. man.
Get the fuck out of here. Saint.
All of this for two
soft-headed motherfuckers
that ain't listen to begin with?
They was family. He was family.
See. all this motherfucker
care about is money
and protecting himself.
Don't want me stirring up trouble
'cause it's bad for business?
Well. we started the business.
Without us. there is no business.
You need to calm the fuck down. Kev.
Or what?
I grew up with you. Saint.
I loved you. and you
betrayed Delroy and Victor.
So you betrayed me.
See. that's when you sold me out.
Kev...
He fucking lied to our faces. Lee.
You know what. I thought
this shit changed you.
And then I realized
it's who you've always been.
It's who you are.
You're a traitor to your people. Saint.
and I ain't following that shit.
[SIGHS]
Hey. Kev.
Kev. stop.
My auntie cries herself
to sleep every night
while he buying houses.
[DARK MUSIC]
That ain't right.
So I'm gonna do what's right.
Get out of here. Lee.
Kev.
Kev!
♪ ♪
Stop man. come on.
It's broad fucking daylight.
So you really gonna do this shit?
In front of all these fucking people?
- Oh. fuck.
- [GUN COCKS]
- I can't let this happen.
- Kev!
♪ ♪
You ain't built for this shit. Saint.
Kev.
Kev!
Wait!
- [GUN COCKS]
- Kev!
[PANTING]
Stop!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
♪ ♪
[ALL SCREAMING]
DEA!
♪ ♪
Kevin!
DEA. drop the gun!
Shit. we gotta get the fuck out of here!
We gotta get the fuck out of here!
DEA! Gun down!
Stop! Stop!
♪ ♪
- [GASPING]
- You're okay. you're okay.
You're okay. Look at me. look at me.
- [GROANS]
- Okay. it's all right.
- It's all right.
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Oh. fuck.
♪ ♪
Fuck!
- [BOTH PANTING]
- Come on. get in the car.
♪ ♪
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
Franklin. what the fuck?
You ain't never shot nobody before!
Why the fuck you shoot Kevin?
You didn't care to restrain him.
You know what you done crazy. right?
[SOBS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --